Guide to the Maurice Sterne Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- 2000 Addition, 1903-1940; Series VII; 0.63; (2 boxes) + 1 art
  - Correspondence
    - Telegrams, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 550)
    - Viking Press, 1932 June 2 (Box 33, Folder 551)
    - Others, 1929-1934, undated (Box 33, Folder 552)
  - Other Material
    - Legal records, 1920, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 553)
    - Manuscript fragments and drawings, undated (Box 33, Folder 554)
    - Medical records, 1903-1934, undated (Box 33, Folder 555)
    - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 33, Folder 556)
    - Writings, undated (Box 33, Folder 557)
    - Untitled oil painting on canvas, signed, undated (Box 34 (Art), Folder 558)
- Oversize, 5; (3 boxes)
  - Letter to Sterne from Bob Wallace and Louis Stewart, 1940 June 18 (Box 29, Folder 503)
  - Sterne [?], Paintings (untitled), undated (Box 29, Folder 504)
  - Sketchbook, undated (Box 29, Folder 505)
  - Loose sketches, undated (Box 29, Folder 506)
  - Photographs
    - Albert Bender, undated (Box 29, Folder 507)
    - Naomi Sterne, undated (Box 29, Folder 508)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 29, Folder 509-11)
    - Fairmont Park Monument, undated (Box 29, Folder 512)
    - Dixon, C. untitled photo, undated (Box 29, Folder 513)
    - Van Dyke, Willard. untitled photos, undated (Box 29, Folder 514)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 29, Folder 515-16)
    - Rogers-Kennedy Memorial, undated (Box 30, Folder 517-19)
    - India [?], undated (Box 30, Folder 520)
    - Justice Department murals, undated (Box 30, Folder 521)
    - Adams, Ansel. Justice Department murals of Maurice Sterne, undated (Box 31, Folder 522)